Such misfortune!
不幸だ！
（不良Ａ）
おら！　止まれや クソガキ！
Hold it, you dipshit!
Wait, you coward!
（不良Ｂ）
待て！　この逃げ足王！
I, Kamijyo Touma...
（上条）
わたくし 上条当麻(とうま)は―
...am leading a way of life...
不幸に愛されているとしか
思えない青春を送っているのだった
～♪
...that is undoubtedly blessed with misfortune.
#01 Academy City
（上条）
そう　７月19日
Yes, July 19th.
I went into a family restaurant in a rather good mood since summer vacation began the next day...
あしたから
夏休みっていう―
ハイな気持ちで
ファミレスに入って
...and ordered a bitter melon and escargot lasagna from hell.
“ゴーヤとエスカルゴの
地獄ラザニア”なんて頼んでた―
That was when it happened.
そのときだった
I saw a girl being harassed by some delinquents,
不良に絡まれてる女の子を見て
thought I'd be a little hero,
and that was when my luck ran out.
“助けてやっかな”なんて
思ってしまったのが運の尽き
なあ いいだろう？
C'mon...
Hey, you.
（上条）ちょっと 君
（不良Ｂ）ああ？
She looks troubled.
彼女 困ってるじゃないですか
（不良Ｃ）ああ スッキリした
（不良Ｄ）ホント ホント
Ahh, that felt good.
Oh, yeah!
何だ？ こいつ
（不良Ｂ）何か用か？ ああ？
What's up with this guy?
Got something to say, huh?
Ahh, god, what is it with my misfortune?!
ああ もう！
何なんですか この不幸は！
ハァ…
Damn, they finally gave up.
くそ… やっと まいたか
（美琴(みこと)）…たく
（上条）あっ！
What were you doing?
（美琴）
何やってんのよ？　あんた
Being a good Samaritan by protecting the delinquents?
（美琴）
不良を守って 善人気取りか
熱血教師ですか？
Are you a certain hot-blooded teacher?
The fact that they stopped chasing after me means...
あいつらが
追っかけてこなくなったのって…
Yeah, I burned them all up to save trouble.
うん
めんどいから 私がやっといた
So that's what happened...
やっぱり…
Hey, do you know what a railgun is?
ねえ
“レールガン”って知ってる？
レールガン？
Railgun?
Also called a super electromagnetic cannon.
別名“超電磁砲”
By borrowing Fleming's momentum, it can fire shells like a cannon.
フレミングの運動量を借りて―
砲弾を
撃ち出したりできるもんなんだけど
Something like this, see?
こういうのをいうらしいのよね！
ウワッ！
Even with a coin like this, if it can go at three times the speed of sound,
（美琴）
こんなコインでも
音速の３倍で飛ばせば―
it can deal a substantial amount of damage, see?
そこそこ威力が出るのよね
Don't tell me you burned those people with that?
（上条）
まさか
連中を追い払うのに それを？
フッ… バカにしないで
Don't take me for a fool.
レベル０(ゼロ)の無能力者どもの
料理法ぐらい 心得てるわよ
I'm quite adept at taking care of useless Level 0 espers.
（上条）
そう　俺は こいつを
助けようとしていたわけじゃない
Yes, I wasn't trying to save her.
I was trying to save the guys that were carelessly trying to approach her.
不用意に こいつに近づいた
少年たちを助けようとしたんだ
I'm quite aware that you're one of only seven Level 5 espers in this Academy City,
お前が
この学園都市に７人しかいない―
レベル５の超能力者なのは
よく分かってるけどさ
人を見下すような言い方
やめたほうがいいぞ ホント
but I think you should change your habit of talking down to other people, really.
まったく… 強者のセリフよね
That's something only the strong would say...
えっ？
おいおいおい 俺だってレベル０…
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm a Level 0, too!
（スパーク音）
ウワッ！
（美琴）
…で そのレベル０のあんたが―
And why are you, a Level 0, unharmed?
なんで傷ひとつないのかしら？
（上条）
何ていうか
不幸っつうか ツイてねえよな
I'm not sure how to put this.
Misfortune?
Bad luck?
You really have bad luck.
お前 ホントにツイてねえよ
Due to the electrical outage caused by the thunderbolts last night,
（上条）
昨日の雷による停電のせいで―
my room is hot as hell right now.
俺の部屋は
うだるような熱気に支配されていた
暑い…
So hot...
It also means that everything inside
my fridge can't be called food anymore.
それは 冷蔵庫の中身が
絶滅していることを意味していて
I had to throw my emergency food supply, instant yakisoba, into the sink.
非常食のカップ焼きそばを
流し台に全部 ぶちまけてしまい
財布を捜しているうちに
キャッシュカードを踏み砕き
While searching for my wallet,
I stepped on and broke my debit card.
担任から “上条ちゃん バカだから
補習です”とラブコール
I got a love call from my teacher saying, "Kamijyo-chan, you need to attend extra lessons 'cause you're dumb~"
不幸だ…
Such misfortune...
よ～し！　天気もいいし
Okay, the weather's nice,
気持ちを入れ替えて
布団でも干しとくか
so let's switch modes by airing out my futon.
よっとっと…
The sky's so blue, yet my future's so dark.
空は こんなに青いのに
お先は真っ暗
I hope it doesn't start raining all of a sudden...
つうか いきなり
夕立とか降ったりしねえよな？
Huh, I'm already airing one out?
あれ？　もう干してある …て
Huh?
Huh???
Huh?!?!
A... girl?
女の子？　なんで こんな所に…
Why is she hanging in a place like this?
Her clothing... Is she a sister?
この服 シスターさんか？
She's a foreigner, right?
外国人 …だよな？
おな…
（上条）えっ？
I'm...
おなか減った
（上条）えっ？
I'm hungry...
I'm hungry.
おなか減った
（上条）もしもし？
Hello?
おなか減った
（おなかの鳴る音）
I'm hungry.
日本語？
She speaks Japanese?
おなか減ったって言ってるんだよ
I keep telling you I'm hungry.
Are you trying to say that, under these circumstances, you're a dying person lying on the streets?
えっと…
あなたは ひょっとして この状況で
“自分は行き倒れです”とか
おっしゃりやがるつもりでせうか？
It can also be termed the fallen dead.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
倒れ死にともいう
ねえ
（上条）あっ…
Hey, I'd be grateful if you could help me fill up my stomach.
おなかいっぱい ご飯を
食べさせてくれると うれしいな
Why don't I help her reach happiness in a far, far away place?
この子には どこか遠い所で
幸せになってもらおう
Is... Is this good enough for you?
こんなので良かったら…
Thank you!
ありがとう！
そして いただきます
And I shall start eating now!
あ～ん…
It's so delicious.
おいしい！　おいしいよ これ
（上条）そ… そうですか
This is so delicious!
Is that so?
全滅した冷蔵庫に入ってた食材を
ぶち込んだ―
It's like a pseudo-fried vegetable plate where
I threw in everything that was inside the fridge.
野菜炒めもどきなんだけど
It must be that thing, right?
あれだよね？
さりげなく 疲労回復のために―
To help relieve fatigue,
you gave it a sour flavor, right?
酸っぱい味付けしてるところが
ニクイよね！
ゲッ！　酸っぱ…
Sour...
Don't force yourself to eat that.
ムリして食べなくていいよ
こんな まずそうな男料理じゃ…
A nasty dish cooked by a man like that...
It's not nasty.
まずそうなんかじゃないよ
私のために
無償で作ってくれたご飯だもん
It's a gratuitous meal you cooked for me!
おいしくないはずがないんだよ！
There's no way it can taste bad!
I'll jump into hell myself!
地獄には俺が１人で落ちる！
（上条）
…でさ なんで
うちのベランダに干されてたわけ？
And?
Why were you being aired out on my balcony?
I fell.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
落ちたんだよ
My original intent was to go from rooftop to rooftop.
ホントは 屋上から屋上に
飛び移るつもりだったんだけど
えっ？　ここ ８階建てだぜ
These are eight-story buildings.
I didn't have a choice.
しかたがなかったんだよ
追われてたからね
I was being pursued.
あっ それより 自己紹介しなきゃね
Ah, I need to introduce myself first.
私の名前は
“インデックス”っていうんだよ
My name is Index.
インデックス？
Index?
…て どう聞いても 偽名じゃねえか
That sounds like a fake name
no matter how you think about it.
何だ？　インデックスって
目次か？
What index? "An" index?
う～ん…
禁書目録ってことなんだけど
It means an index for forbidden texts.
あっ 魔法名なら “Dedicatus(デーディカートゥス)545”
Ah, my magical name is Dedicatus545.
It means a sheep dedicated to
protecting the knowledge of the strong.
“献身的な子羊は 強者の知恵を
守る”っていう意味だね
And, why are you being pursued, Index?
そのインデックスさんが
なんで追われてんだ？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
私の持ってる10万3,000冊の
魔道書が狙いだと思う
I believe they're after the 103,000 grimoires I possess.
えっ 魔道書？
Grimoires?
Yes,
the book of Eibon,
「エイボンの書」「 レメゲトン」
the Lemegeton,
「死者の書」
the Book of the Dead,
these are the representative ones.
代表的なのは こういうのだけど
（上条）
中身は ともかく お前
手ぶらにしか見えないんだけど
I don't know about inside of you,
but you're empty handed, you know?
I have them.
ちゃんと持ってるよ 10万3,000冊
All 103,000 books.
103,000 books...
10万3,000冊って…
どこかの倉庫の鍵でも持ってんのか
Do you have a key to a big warehouse?
No.
（上条）
まさか バカには見えない本とか
言うんじゃねえだろうな？
You're not going to tell me that these are books that dumb people can't see, are you?
People that aren't dumb can't see them either.
バカじゃなくても見えないよ
勝手に見られると 意味がないもの
It'd be meaningless if people could see them.
And... who's after you?
（上条）
…で 誰に狙われてるわけ？
The magic society.
魔術結社だよ
（上条）はぁ？　魔術？
Magic?
Eh? Was my Japanese weird?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あれ？　日本語が おかしかった？
マジックだよ　マジックキャバル
Magic.
The Magic Cabal.
それって 新興宗教か何かか？
Is that a religious group or something?
そこはかとなくバカにしてるね？
（上条）あ～…
Somehow I feel you're making fun of me.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
そこはかとなくバカにしてるね？
You're making fun of me, right?
Sorry, this is impossible.
ごめん　ムリだ
I know of many esper abilities,
俺も いろいろ
“異能の力”は知ってるけど
but magic is out of the question.
魔術はムリだ
Supernatural powers within this Academy City are quite normal.
この学園都市じゃ 超能力なんて
珍しくも何ともねえからな
Science can develop anything.
科学の力で
誰だって開発できちまう
It's weird that you believe in supernatural powers and yet you don't believe in magic!
超能力は信じるのに
魔術は信じないって変な話
Then, what is magic?
じゃ 魔術って何だよ？
何なら いっちょう 見せてみろよ
Show me some.
I don't have any mana, so I can't use any.
私には魔力がないから使えないの
使えないんじゃ 魔術なんか
あるかどうか分かんないだろうが
If you can't use any, then I wouldn't be able to know if magic really does exist!
It does!
あるもん！　魔術はあるもん
Magic exists!
ハァ… まあ 俺にだって―
Well, I've also possessed some weird power for my entire life.
生まれたときからの
妙な力があるんだけど
Weird power?
妙な力？
（上条）この右手で触ると―
If I come into contact with
an esper ability with this right hand,
異能の力なら 電撃だろうが
レールガンだろうが…
be it a railgun or a lightning attack,
even a miracle of God can be dispelled.
多分
神の奇跡だって打ち消せます はい
Yep.
何だ？　その
怪しい通販見てるみてえな反応は
What's that "screw the shopping channel" look on your face?!
だって…
Well...
An atheist like you...
神さまを信じてもいなさそうな人に
“神さまの奇跡だって
打ち消せます”とか言われても…
...is saying a miracle of God can be dispelled...
クッ… ムカつく
This pisses me off.
To think I'd be taken for a fool by this phony magical girl.
こんなインチキ魔法少女に
小バカにされるとは…
I'm not a phony!
インチキじゃないもん！
（上条）じゃ 何か見せてみろよ
Then show me something.
If I punch that out with my right hand,
それを右手でぶち抜きゃ
右手のことも信じるしかねえよな？
then you'll have to believe my right hand's power.
Fine!
いいもん！　じゃ 見せてあげる
I'll show you then!
これ！　この服
This!
This clothing!
It's a very powerful defensive barrier called "the walking church"!
これは“歩く教会”っていう
極上の防御結界なんだから
What are you talking about?
何だ？　それ
All you've been doing was throwing all this weird terminology at me.
さっきから ワケの分からない
専門用語ばっかしぶち込みやがって
意味分かんねえよ
I still have no clue whatsoever.
I'll prove it instead of all this talking!
だったら 論より証拠！
この包丁で私のおなかを刺してみる
Use this kitchen knife to stab my stomach!
Wh-What...
な… 何だよ それ
This is a church in the form of clothing that possesses
the absolute minimum elements that make up a church.
これは教会として必要最低限の
要素だけを詰め込んだ―
服の形をした教会なんだから
A stab from a kitchen knife won't hurt me at all!
包丁で刺したくらいじゃ
傷ひとつ つけられないんだよ
じゃ グッサリ刺してみます
…なんてバカいるわけねえだろう
Then, I shall stab you.
Or did you really think I'd say that?
とことんバカにして！
You really are making fun of me!
これは トリノ聖骸布(せいがいふ)を
正確にコピーした物だから
This is an accurate copy of the Holy Shroud of Turin!
強度は絶対なんだよ！
Its hardness is of Pope Class.
It can turn aside any kind of attack,
be it physical or magical or anything,
物理 魔術を問わず 全ての攻撃を
受け流し 吸収しちゃうんだから
and it absorbs the impact!
ふ～ん… つまり あれだ
Basically...
...if that's really an esper ability...
それが本当に異能の力だってんなら
...then it'll be broken into pieces
when I touch it with my right hand...
俺の右手が触れただけで
木っ端みじんってわけだな？
フフ～ン…
君の力が本当な･ら･ね
If your power is actually au-then-tic~
クッ… この！
Fine, you little...
上等だ こら！
If you're going to go that far,
そこまで言うんなら
やってやろうじゃねえか！
then I'll really do it!
Huh?
あれ？
Nothing's happening!
別に 何も起きないんだけど
フフ～ン…
うん？　なに？
What?
W-Well...
い… いや…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん？
Jesus...
…たく あちこち かみつきやがって
You bit me all over the place...
What are you, a fly from summer camp?
合宿んときの蚊かよ？　お前は
That was really my bad.
さっきのは 俺が悪かったよ
だから…
So-
ウワッ！
（物がぶつかる音）
I don't understand how you can talk to me after what just happened.
あれだけのことが
あったっていうのに―
どうして
普通に話しかけられるんだよ？
Well... I got caught in the confusion somewhat...
あっ いや…
俺だって
大変 ドギマギしてるというか
何というか…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）バカにして もう
How should I put it...
Make fun of me, will you?
Gosh!
Her clergy clothing.
あの修道服
俺の右手に反応したってことは―
The fact that it responded to my right hand means there's absolutely no doubt that she's related to esper abilities.
あいつが異能の力に関わってるのは
間違いない
Done!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
できた！
フフ～ン…
What's with the... iron maiden?
何だ？　そのアイアンメイデン
日本語では“針のむしろ”という
Called the mat of needles in Japanese.
ハァ…
Ah, I forgot!
あっ そうだ 補習！
Extra lessons!
I need to head to school now.
俺 これから
学校行かなきゃなんねえんだけど
お前 どうすんの？
ここに残るなら 鍵渡すけど
What are you going to do?
I can hand you the keys if you're staying here.
フフッ… いい　出てく
It's okay.
I'll leave.
いつまでもいると
連中 ここまで来そうだし
If I keep staying here, they'll find this place.
You don't want this room to explode, right?
君だって この部屋ごと
爆破されたくはないよね
お… おい！　待てよ
Hey!
Wait!
君の右手…
（上条）うん？
Your right hand.
I think it's something that erases things like good luck and blessings of God.
幸運とか 神のご加護とか
そういうもの まとめて―
消してしまってるんだと思うよ
（上条）はぁ？
Just by your right hand coming in contact with the air,
その右手が空気に触れてるだけで
バンバン
不幸になっていくってわけだね
you'll keep encountering misfortune!
（上条）
不幸だ…
Such misfortune...
If you ask me, I think being born with such power is a misfortune in and of itself.
何が不幸って そんな力を持って
生まれてきちゃったことが―
もう不幸だよね
You...
お前…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん？
お前 ここを出て
どっか行くアテでもあるのかよ？
Do you have anywhere to go to once you leave here?
The enemy will come if I stay here.
ここにいると 敵が来るから
（上条）敵？
Enemy?
This clothing functions through mana.
この服は魔力で動いているからね
それを基に
サーチかけてるみたいなんだよ
I think they're applying a search based on this mana.
But, don't worry.
でも 大丈夫　教会まで逃げきれば
かくまってもらえるから
If I can make it to The Church, they'll help hide me.
ちょっと待てよ
それが分かってて 放り出せるかよ
Now, hold on.
Do you think I'd let you go after learning all this?
Then, would you accompany me to the depths of hell?
じゃ 私と一緒に
地獄の底まで ついてきてくれる？
フフッ… それじゃ
Bye, then.
You're welcome to come back if you're in trouble again!
困ったことがあったら
また来ていいからな！
うん！
おなか減ったら また来る…
Yeah, I'll come again when I'm hungry!
ウワッ！
What is this? Agathions?
なに これ… アガシオン？　アア…
あっ ヤベッ！　補習！
Oh shit!
Extra lessons!
The Academy City.
（上条）
“学園都市”
In this place, there are a plethora of colleges, primary schools, middle schools, etc.
ここは 何十もの大学や小中学校が
ひしめく学校の町
A city of schools.
東京都の３分の１もの広さに
人口は230万
Spreading as wide as one-third of the Tokyo metropolis,
its population is 2.3 million.
80% of these are students,
その８割が学生で
ほとんどが ここに住んでる
and most of them live inside the city.
A weird city with things like those
cleaning robots that are everywhere.
そして
さっきの掃除ロボットや―
何かがウロウロしてる
ちょっと変わった町だ
Okay then, let us begin the extra lessons.
（小萌(こもえ)）
は～い！
それじゃ 補習の授業を始めます
I put in some effort and made a quiz for you all,
先生 気合いを入れて
小テスト作ってきたので―
早速 配るです
so I'll be handing these out right away.
If your marks are bad,
（小萌）
成績が悪かったら 罰ゲームに
“すけすけ見る見る”ですよ
you'll have to go through
the "see through" punishment game.
The "see through" one? Is that the one where you play poker blindfolded?
（土御門(つちみかど)）
“すけすけ見る見る”って―
目隠しで
ポーカーするやつだったかにゃ？
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
10回連続で勝つまで
帰っちゃダメって おイタな企画
She won't let you go home until you win ten games in a row at that...
Sheesh...
やれやれ…
この間も朝まで生居残りだったにゃ
We were forced to stay through the night last time...
Kamijyo-chan,
上条ちゃんは
“開発”の単位が足りないので
since your documentation credits are insufficient,
どのみち
“すけすけ見る見る”ですよ
you'll end up playing the "see through" game either way.
Komoe-chan loves you so much, Kami-yan.
小萌ちゃんは カミやんが
かわゆうて しかたないんやね
青髪… お前は あの背中に
悪意は感じられんのか？
Aogami...
You don't sense any evil intent behind her?
To be able to enjoy scolding from a child like that,
あないなお子さまに
言葉で責められるやなんて…
カミやん 経験値 高いで
Kami-yan, you'll gain plenty of experience points, man!
So not only are you a lolicon, you're also an M?
Note: M is slang for "Masochist"
ロリコンのうえに Ｍかよ
救いようねえな
God, you're hopeless.
アハハッ！
ロリが好きなんとちゃうで
It's not "I like lolis",
but rather "I also like lolis".
ロリも好きなんやで
（上条）あのな…
Excuse me...
Hey, people?
は～い そこ！　それ以上
ひと言でも しゃべりやがったら
Speak another damn word,
コロンブスの卵ですよ
ＯＫですか？
and you'll be doing a Columbus' egg, okay?
Do I make myself clear?
ハァ… 不幸だ
Such misfortune.
I wonder what she's doing now.
（上条）
あいつ どうしてるかな
部屋にフード忘れてったしな
I think she forgot her hood back in my room.
でも 何だったんだ？
But what was all that?
10万3,000冊の魔道書って
そんな物(もん) 一体 どこに…
103,000 grimoires...
Where does she put all that?
あいつ
“ここにある”なんて言ってたけど
She says she has them "right here"...
フフッ… そのうち
忘れ物 取りに戻ってくっかな
She'll come back to pick up what she forgot someday.
Sensei~
先生！　上条君が
女子テニス部のヒラヒラに―
Kamijyo-kun has his eyes stuck on the skirts of the girls' tennis club!
夢中になってま～す
（上条）えっ…
（生徒たち）
泣かせた… 泣かせた…
You made her cry...
Stares of ill intent
（生徒たち）
泣かせた… 泣かせた…
It is now past the latest one can stay after school.
（警備ﾛﾎﾞｯﾄ）
完全下校時刻を過ぎています
All students should head home right away.
学生の皆さんは
速やかに帰宅してください
It is now past the latest one can stay after school.
完全下校時刻を…
And I was forced to stay at school until this late, eh?
結局 この時間まで居残りか
不幸だ…
All students should head home right away.
Such misfortune...
There you are!
I finally found you, and this time, we'll-
見つけたわよ　今度こそ…
Hey, hold it!
…て ちょっと！
You, I'm talking to you!
あんたよ あんた！
止まりなさいってば！
I told you to hold it!
Ah, you again, the middle school shocker.
ああ　またか ビリビリ中学生
Quit calling me "shocker"!
“ビリビリ”いうな！
I have a proper name called Misaka Mikoto, okay?
私には“御坂(みさか)美琴”って
ちゃんとした名前があんのよ
ハァ…
You've been calling me "shocker" ever since we first met, haven't you?
あんた 初めて会ったときから
ずっとビリビリいってるでしょう
Okay, shocker.
…で ビリビリ　お前も補習か？
You had to go to extra lessons, too?
Quiet, you!
うっさいわね！
今日という今日こそ―
Today, I'll stun you like a fried frog's leg,
電極刺したカエルの足みたいに
ヒクヒクさせてやるから
so get your will and distribution of wealth ready, goddammit!
遺言と遺産分配やっとけや こら！
ヤダ
（美琴）なんですって！
Screw you.
Oh yeah?!
フン… どうよ？
How about it?
ふぬけた頭のスイッチ
切り替えられた？
Did the switch in your rotten brain change positions now?
（上条）
ふざけんな！
Screw you!
Because of all those thunderbolts you rained over the city,
昨日 てめえが
ド派手に雷落としたおかげで―
うちの電化製品とか冷蔵庫の中
全滅だぞ！
all of my electronic appliances and
all the food inside my fridge died!
あんたがムカつくから悪いのよ！
I blame you for being a dick!
I have no clue how that got you angry.
意味の分かんねえキレ方しやがって
Besides, I never laid a single finger on you!
大体 俺は てめえに
指１本 触れてねえだろうが
That's right.
そうよ　１発も殴られてないもん
I never landed a single punch on you either!
…てことは お互いさまで
引き分けってことでしょう
So, for the benefit of both sides, let's call this a tie.
はぁ？
じゃ いいよ　お前の勝ちで
You can have the victory, then.
ちょっと あんた！
真面目にやりなさいってば！
Hey, you!
Take this seriously!
So, I can go at you with all that I've got?
じゃ
真面目にやってもいいんかよ？
The phony magician in the morning,
朝はエセ魔術師　夕方は
ビリビリ超能力者ときたもんだ
and the shocker in the evening...
Magician?
魔術師？
（警備ﾛﾎﾞｯﾄ）
メッセージ メッセージ
Message, message.
Offensive type electrical wave that violates the electrical wave law detected.
電波法に抵触する
攻撃性電磁波を感知
Irregularity in the system confirmed.
システムの異常を確認しました
（美琴･上条）
ウワッ！
You idiot!
（上条）
バカ野郎！
あんな所でビリビリすっから！
Don't be shocking other things in a place like this!
Quiet, you!
（美琴）
うっさいわね！
早く逃げなさいよ もう！
Run already!
ハァ…
うん？　清掃ロボット？
Cleaning robots?
Sheesh...
…たく 人の部屋の前で
なに掃除してんだ？
What are they cleaning in front of my room?
ハハッ… 何ていうか 不幸だ
How should I put it?
Such misfortune.
Hey, Index.
おい インデックス
こんな所で何やってんだよ？
What are you lying here for?
Sleeping in a place like this-
こんな所で寝て…
あっ… うん？　何だよ これ
What is... this...
Snap out of it, Index!
しっかりしろ インデックス！
What happened to you?
どうしたんだよ？　一体
どこのどいつに やられたんだ？
Who the hell did this to you?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
うん？　僕たち魔術師だけど
That'd be us, the magicians.
～♪
Next Episode
（上条）
ステイル＝マグヌス
あの魔術師野郎の名前だ
Stiyl Magnus,
that's the name of that magician bastard.
Protect Index?
インデックスを保護？
こいつら 一体…
What are these guys plotting?
次回 「魔女狩りの王(イノケンティウス)」
Next time, "Innocentius".
When science and magic cross paths,
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる
this epic will begin!